chat4support.com 2016-05-14

# Chat4Support -- Privacy Policy

Chat4Support is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the following Chat4Support Privacy Policy Statement when you use our products and enjoy our service. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

If you are willing to purchase our products or services, you must fill in your personal information to us, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests or favorites. And if you do a procure action, you will be asked for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address, which is useful for us to build up the transaction with you.

We may also collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in related to Chat4Support sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access time and referring web site addresses.

Of course, these above your personal information must be kept secret and never be revealed to any third party or entity except the following circumstances:

  * Any requirements regarding to governmental or attorney behaviors or needs to pursuit any legal actions or pending legal actions;
  * Once our attorney requests such information relevant to a current or pending legal matter in which you are a potential or actual party or otherwise contributed in some way to the causation of the legal matter;
  * Some force majeure happened.
  * No liability for the acts of Third Parties. We are not responsible for the disclosure of registration data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

Chat4Support collects and uses your personal information to offer you products with best quality and services. We use your personal information in order to administer our business activities, communicating with you on-line, providing customer service and offering other available products or services to our customers or prospective customers. Sometimes, we may give you some notifications about the changes on our web site, products updated information, new products information or services. All of these should safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will have any opportunities to choose whether to use them or not.

**Accessing of Your Personal Information**

You may have the ability to view or edit your personal information online. In order to prevent your personal information not to be viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your credentials (e-mail address and password). 

**Security of Your Personal Information**

Chat4Support is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.  
For the confidentiality, Chat4Support will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose your personal information, including important data to any third party. We will supply a secure area, and store all Registration Data in a private database which is not connected to the Internet.   
If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

**How we use Cookies?**

Cookies means a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookies to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer and we utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information and passwords for you. So we use cookies to help you surf on our website and feel safe to transact with us.  
We use cookies and web server logs to store your private information and your browsing paths on our website. That may improve our website and offer better service. Cookies can also identify the return customers for us and collect user information which is useful to the operator.  
You are able to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies.  
**_When you register your personal information, you can use your alternative email address, but this email address may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. So we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured email._**

**Use of other websites linked to our web site**

You can browse other web sites linked to our web site, but we are not responsible for keeping secrecy for you. So please remember that once you use to link to other websites, this Privacy Policy is not in effect any more. You are required to abid by the rules or policies of other websites you are browsing, not our Privacy Policy. So it is safe for you to look through the rules and policies before proceeding. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update our privacy policy statement if there are any changes to offer better service and customer feedback. When we post changes to this statement on our web site to let you know immediately, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the end of this statement. 

**Information Lost or Stolen**

If your personal information, especially your credit card or password is lost or stolen, please notify Chat4Support immediately. We will cancel your credit card number or password and then update its records. 

**Cancellation of your data**

If you would prefer to cease business with us, you may cancel your account at any time by sending email to us. Once we revise the information of it, we will delete all your registration data from our database. 

**Contacting us**

Chat4Support welcomes you give comments or advices on this privacy policy statement. If you have any questions about this statement, please contact us: tech-support[@]chat4support.com 

Last Updated:8.2006
